http://www.parrotmag.com/privacy

Login/LogoutRegisterYour orders
HomeParrot SocialCollecting Parrots on PostcardsParrots BlogParrots magazine readers lettersParrots Free AdsPhoto GalleryVideo GallerySuppliersClubsCalendarParrot CareParrot worldwide lost and found registerVetsBreeders DirectoryCITESBreedingBuyers GuidesLost and Found registerBuy the Latest IssueHelp & FAQShopForumContact UsLost and FoundWorldwide
Privacy
This website is owned and run by Imax Ltd trading as Parrots magazine. Imax Ltd is committed in protecting your privacy in accordance with its obligations under the Data Protection Act 1998. This privacy policy explains what information Imax Ltd collects about you and how it will be used. When you access and use this website, you agree to be legally bound by all our terms and conditions as well as our privacy policy outlined below. TransactionsImax Ltd makes every effort to maintain customer confidentiality when securing an online payment. This includes ensuring the security of your credit card details and other personal information. All of your personal information is encrypted as it travels over the Internet. When you make a purchase, you enter a secure Internet site indicated by the letters https:// in the address bar and or a padlock displayed in your web browser. To protect you against credit card fraud, where someone has discovered your credit card details but does not have your card, you will be asked to enter the unique security code printed on the back of your payment card.  Personal dataImax Ltd collects information from you to enable us to provide you with the goods and services you ask for. This may include your name, address, telephone number, email address, credit or other payment card details. Imax Ltd does not have access to your payment card details following completion of a transaction as they are encrypted.  Imax Ltd will use the information you enter into the website only for administration purposes and any other purposes made clear in the data entry forms themselves, in any relevant terms or conditions and on any pages or emails that link to such forms. Imax Ltd may also collect Internet protocol addresses to diagnose problems with our servers and for system administration, but Imax Ltd does not link these addresses to any person’s name or identity. Whenever Imax Ltd asks you for information about yourself you may, by ticking the relevant box, opt out of receiving other communications. In addition, whenever you receive other communications by email, you will be told how to opt out of being updated by email in the future. If you choose to opt out of being updated as described above, Imax Ltd will cease all such future disclosure of data. If, for any reason, you are unsure about the personal and account information we are holding in your name, please contact us. We will happily review your file and update the records if required. You can contact us by phone on 01273 464777, by fax on 01273 463999 or by email This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.. Alternatively, this information can be checked and reviewed online once you have signed in. Under no circumstances will Imax Ltd collect any data that is not directly related to the use of this website.  Third PartiesIn order to process orders, Imax Ltd may pass your personal information and payment details to third party providers, regulatory authorities and where it is lawfully requested to do so. Such third party providers will only have access to the personal information needed to perform the relevant service. They may not use your personal information for any other purposes and are required to process your personal information in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. Imax Ltd will not provide any of the personal information, you give to us, to any third party for any purpose whatsoever, except with your prior express consent.International transfer of informationImax Ltd will retain the personal information you provide within the United Kingdom, and will not transfer it to any other country except with your prior and express consent. However, your personal information may be transferred between offices of Imax Ltd in other countries, in order to carry out transactions requested by you. However, the internet is global and it is possible that information you provide to Imax Ltd may be temporarily transferred through a worldwide route as it passes between you and this website or a third party provider. How we collect data about your use of this websiteImax Ltd will always try to ensure that this website offers visitors an enjoyable experience. To help us achieve this goal, Imax Ltd and our appointed agency may collect anonymous information about your use of this website and your reading of the newsletter from cookies and or by the use of pixel tags.  Cookies are small data files that are sent to your browser and pixel tags are used to read such cookies. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies but you can delete existing cookies from your browser and, by editing your Internet browser options, you can choose not to receive cookies in future. Please note that if you do opt to reject cookies, any personalised functionality of this website, for example the shop, will not operate correctly. SecurityImax Ltd is committed to the security of your personal information and we have security procedures in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control. Your name, personal information and credit card details are never stored on the Internet with our system. Once you type in your information it is instantly sent to our order processing system, which is on a separate server from the Internet. We employ the latest technology on the site to protect you from unauthorised use of the information you are sending to the server.
Newsletter Signup
Get the latest Parrots news, delivered to your inbox!
Login/LogoutHomeSite MapPrivacyTerms & ConditionsContact UsTerms of UseAdvertise
Parrots magazine is published by Imax Visual Ltd, West Building, Elm Grove Lane, Steyning BN44 3SA Telephone +44 (0)1273 464777© Parrots magazine 2019
